

Adrian de Souza Frontend Web Developer

072 156 8027

☑ adriandesouzal@gmail.com ⑤ https://github.com/acenyte

GENERAL INFORMATION

Aged 29 years young, I am a front-end developer based in Johannesburg. My first experience with HTML was 7 years ago and I have been vexed ever since. My ultimate career goal is to be an expert Fullstack Dev, but above that my personal dream is to make a gem of a video game, cliche for a dev I know, but I'm doing it anyway.

EDUCATION

Matriculated in 2008 from my hometown school of Hoërskool Carletonville. BTech Multimedia Studies in 2013 at the University of Johannesburg.

WORK EXPERIENCE

JS Frontend Engineer at Flat Rock Solutions | Freelance 2019 - present

Responsible for taking an existing mobile android app called Mobila and converting it into a web app using Angular 7, Angular Material and Firebase.

Reference: Allan Wilson 083 377 2165

Front-end Developer at Wunderman | January 2016 - present

Responsible for building single page applications, campaign websites and maintaining websites for clients including Cadbury, E&Y, Ford, Standard Bank and DSTV. Moving away from static sites, I became familiar with dynamic web development, using API's, SASS and further advanced my Javascript using the the Angular Framework. Reference: Mfundo Sithole 073 463 1015 visit https://www.cadbury.co.za/psbar/

Web Master at Wunderman I March 2014 - December 2015

Responsible for all maintenance and CMS tasks for all Coca-Cola brand sites for South America, Middle East, and Africa markets. My proudest achievement during this period was doing the markup and styling for Share A Coke SA.

Reference: Mfundo Sithole 073 463 1015

TECH **STACK**



ANGULAR TYPESCRIPT SASS

2 YEARS EXP

DRUPAL

